# WINDU FIRMANSYACH

Informatics Engineering

- +62 822 1973 8563
- ✓ firmansyachwindu4@gmail.com
- Bandung, Indonesia
- www.linkedin.com/in/windufirmansyach

#### **SUMMARY**

As a web developer, I have combined creative design with technical skills to create responsive and functional websites for various clients and projects. With a bachelor's degree in Informatics from Telkom University, I have gained a solid foundation in programming languages, such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript and more, as well as prototyping tools, such as Figma.

One of my latest projects is designing and developing a website for Telkom Indonesia, a leading telecommunication company, which is useful for data inventory and user experience. I was responsible for designing the website layout, optimizing the application speed, and creating a full-stack for the website. I collaborated with the team and client to ensure their vision was realized in the design and development of the website. This project expanded my knowledge and skills in creating visually appealing, user-friendly, and efficient websites.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Gravacloud November 2023 - Present

#### L1 Monitoring Cloud Sever & Security Analyst

- 1. Keep an eye on the health and performance of the cloud server.
- 2. Notifications to immediately address critical server events and incidents.
- 3. Evaluate server performance metrics and optimizations to improve overall efficiency.
- 4. Establishing and upholding security best practices within the cloud server environment.
- 5. Develop and maintain detailed documentation covering server configuration, monitoring configuration, and troubleshooting protocols

Telkom Indonesia Juli 2022 - September 2022

#### **Web Developer**

- 1. Designing Figma for organization that useful for data inventory.
- 2. Creating UI UX that makes comfortable to work with it.
- 3. Optimizing applications for maximum speed.
- 4. Creating Full-stack for website Telkom.

PT. TELKOM AKSES Juni 2021 - Agustus 2021

#### **Data Entry Clerk**

- 1. Input Data Entry for Inventory in Organization.
- 2. Data Recapitulation Using Microsoft Excel.
- 3. Inventory Data that input for organization such as location, router, FDH, ODC, and LAN connector.

### **EDUCATION**

Universitas Telkom Agustus 2018 - Present

## **SKILL**

### Personal

Time Management
Communication Skills

#### **Professional**

Huawei Cloud Web Development Web Design Data Entry Figma Design UI/UX Database